<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://uneo.myshopify.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://uneo.myshopify.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://uneo.myshopify.com/blogs/news/tagged/look.atom"/>
  <title>uneo - News</title>
  <updated>2020-08-26T12:52:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>uneo</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://uneo.myshopify.com/blogs/news/should-you-use-a-shave-cream-or-shave-gel</id>
    <published>2020-08-26T12:52:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-12-30T11:01:15-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://uneo.myshopify.com/blogs/news/should-you-use-a-shave-cream-or-shave-gel"/>
    <title>Should you use a Shave Cream or Shave Gel ?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Shopify API</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<ol>
<li>
<p>The first thing you need to do is sit down and set your goals. Diana Scharf Hunt said “Goals are dreams with deadlines.” A lot of times, people are thrown off by the idea of taking the time to set their goals.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Keeping one’s self going is a difficult thing to do. There are a million distractions that occur every day and that can mean that we do not stay on track with what we should be doing.</strong></p>
<p>Have you ever heard the expression, “Do not count your chickens before they hatch?” Maybe an older, wiser individual would tell you this to keep you from getting ahead of yourself. Like buying a new car before you actually got that new job. Well, when setting and obtaining your goals, you need to “Count your chicken before they hatch” in your mind. What I mean by this is you have to start seeing yourself completing or obtaining your goal. What you profess, you possess!</p>
<p>The first thing you need to do is sit down and set your goals. Diana Scharf Hunt said “Goals are dreams with deadlines.” A lot of times, people are thrown off by the idea of taking the time to set their goals.</p>
</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://uneo.myshopify.com/blogs/news/5-days-of-simple-summer-looks</id>
    <published>2020-07-17T11:59:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-12-22T10:38:43-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://uneo.myshopify.com/blogs/news/5-days-of-simple-summer-looks"/>
    <title>5 Days Of Simple Summer Looks</title>
    <author>
      <name>Shopify API</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Summer days can be unpredictable. With kids out of school, we are always in search or something new to keep everyone entertained or the next adventure. It can be difficult to even find a time to work let alone get ready for the day, so I put it to the test- how fast can I throw together 5 easy outfits for every occasion throughout the week. The goal was to still look stylish and put together, but keep it simple and quick! Here are 5 days of simple summer looks for various occasions.</span>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://uneo.myshopify.com/blogs/news/matching-mom-daughter-suit</id>
    <published>2020-07-17T11:58:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2020-12-22T10:38:41-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://uneo.myshopify.com/blogs/news/matching-mom-daughter-suit"/>
    <title>Matching Mom-Daughter Suit</title>
    <author>
      <name>Shopify API</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Fruit prints are back on the rise this summer and the high-schooler in me is here for it. It feels like such a throwback and I love the way it’s bringing in so many colors to this seasons print trends! </span><a href="https://bit.ly/2RlKj8f" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" class="external">Summersalt</a><span> just launched their </span><a href="https://bit.ly/2BwoNZc" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" class="external">Cherries collection</a><span> and Mara and I both got a few pieces. It’s been so much fun twinning with her, especially now that’s she’s starting to fit into some of the brands I love and wear a lot. </span><a href="https://bit.ly/38gfI2Q" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" class="external">This wrap skirt</a><span> is one of my favorite pieces – it comes in multiple prints and so good as a beach cover up but can also transition to brunch or dinner out with a cropped tee or bodysuit. The perfect vacation piece! Right now you can get $10 towards your order with code: HELLOFASHION10 (orders over $95).</span>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
